well I think I will go to cafeteria with
my friends and eat something
perhaps I will drink some coffee after
that I will rest my mind until next
class this Saturday afternoon I'm going
to watch a basketball match I'm going to
buy some popcorn and cola before the
match in the inning I'm going to hang
out with my friends we are going to have
dinner and spend time together on Sunday
I'm just going to rest I'm going to
sleep till ten o'clock and watch movies
and TV series I am not sure yet actually
I want to do masters when I graduate
probably I will apply to some
universities to get a master's degree if
I get accepted I will do academic
studies if I don't get accepted I will
try to find a job I'm going to travel
abroad this summer with friends we are
going to visit Italy and Spain in Italy
we are going to see the Colosseum and
the Pantheon in Spain we are going to
see the Alhambra and the Great Mosque of
Cordoba we are very excited first I will
go to work I will work from 9:00 a.m. to
5:00 p.m. after work I will go to
supermarket because I need to do some
shopping I will buy milk cheese meat
some vegetables and fruit finally I will
go home and spent
with my family okay
I have several plans for my short-term
future professionally I'm going to take
courses and seminars to become better at
my job
academically I'm going to complete
online courses to improve my knowledge
and culturally I'm going to watch lots
of movies read many books attend several
concerts